Alright so how do we use this, that again can be the biggest thing of "I brought something but I don't even know how to use it".
I'm going to break it down pretty simple for you.
Omcron fat loss monitor is basic.
You start with the one and it gives you a lot of options but it blinks to let you know what it needs immediately.
I am going to say I am a guest so I will press set.
Then it wants to know are you a normal guest or an athlete and I'm going to go up because I'm an athlete.
Press set.
Then it wants to know my height, five-five.
So use the down button and it even gives you half an inch or quarter of an inch so it's pretty exact on that.
Five five even, press set.
Now the pounds, now the fun part, put your weight in.
Today I'm one thirty seven, lot's of muscle mass there.
And my age going down at thirty one, for now.
And then it blinks male or female.
Now after all that is complete you press set.
All of your data is now stored.
Now to find out your exact amount you are going to grab this monitor, wrap your thumbs your hands around, your thumbs are on top and because you are doing this by yourself, you are going to press your start button.
And it's going to blink, you will see those little blinks down below where it says low, normal, high and very high.
And now it tells me that I am at twenty one point two percent and my bmi is at twenty two point eight percent.
So those numbers are pretty different from the other body fat monitor I showed you but it let's you know where it can be a little more accurate or a little less accurate.
And that's it, got that vital information.